(Sheldon:)But which one of us should be
the party who...
(Howard:)You can do it, Sheldon.
So stipulated!
(Leonard:)Once I found a stash
of contracts under his bed.
(Leonard:)It was weird.
(Bernadette:)I wonder how much
she spent on this.
(Amy:)Ooh, let's find out.
(Raj:)It doesn't matter.
(Raj:)It's the thought
that counts.
(Penny:)Yeah, yeah,
and beauty's on the inside,
(Penny:)size doesn't matter...
how much she spend?
(Raj:)Seriously, guys,
I don't want to know.
(Amy:)Oh, my.
(Raj:)Oh, come on, you can't say
“Oh, my,” and then not tell me!
These things go for $500 and up.
BERNADETTE:
Damn.
(Bernadette:)All I got for Valentine's Day
was a postcard
(Bernadette:)saying my Vermont Teddy Bear
was back-ordered.
PENNY:
Okay, so, she drops off
a $500 gift
(Penny:)and she's not trying to
get back together with you?
(Raj:)Maybe you're right.
(Bernadette:)Or she's telling the truth
and just being nice.
(Raj:)Maybe you're right.
(Raj:)Wow, I am easy to manipulate.
(phone chiming)
(Raj:)Oh, guys, it's Emily.